A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21 FA242
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1955-1974; 6; 4 Cubic Feet 11 document boxes
  - Polls: Public Reaction to the Transportation Bond Issue, 1971 September 2 (Box 104, Folder 1239)
  - Polls: Public Reaction to the Transportation Bond Issue, 1973 September 15 (Box 104, Folder 1240)
  - Polls: Public Reaction to the Transportation Bond Issue, 1973 October 22 (Box 104, Folder 1241)
  - Polls: Relative Effectiveness of Political Campaigners for the Transportation Bond Issue, 1973 September 15 (Box 104, Folder 1242)
  - Polls: Second Survey on Candidates for Mayor of New York City, 1973 March 6 (Box 104, Folder 1243)
  - Polls: State Abortion Law, 1972 March 11-12 (Box 104, Folder 1244)
  - Polls: Standing of Gubernatorial Candidates, 1970 August (Box 104, Folder 1245)
  - Polls: Standing of Gubernatorial Candidates, 1970 September (Box 104, Folder 1246)
  - Polls: Survey of Potential Candidates for the United States Senate, 1969 September-October (Box 104, Folder 1247)
  - Post-Election Analysis: Analysis and Summaries of the 1970 Gubernatorial Election, 1970 November 25-December 23 (Box 104, Folder 1248)
  - Post-Election Analysis: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970 November 5-1971 May 18 (Box 104, Folder 1249)
  - Post-Election Analysis: Public Reaction to Political Advertising, 1971 January (Box 104, Folder 1250)
  - Post-Election Analysis: The Role of Advertising in Rockefeller's 1970 Campaign, 1970 December (Box 104, Folder 1251)
  - Post-Election Analysis: Program Highlights: Education, Health, Crime, Housing, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 1252)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: Blue Book, 1971 September (Box 105, Folder 1253)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: General Correspondence, 1971 October 18-November 22 (Box 105, Folder 1254)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: General Correspondence, 1971 October 1-14 (Box 105, Folder 1255)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: General Correspondence, 1971 September 1-30 (Box 105, Folder 1256)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: General Correspondence, 1971 May 24-August 31 (Box 105, Folder 1257)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: General Correspondence, 1971 March 17-April 27 (Box 105, Folder 1258)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: Literature, Press Kit, 1971 September-November (Box 105, Folder 1259)
  - Transportation Bond Issue: Programs, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 1260)
  - White Papers, 1970 October 13 (Box 106, Folder 1261)
  - White Papers: Art and Culture, 1970 November 2 (Box 106, Folder 1262)
  - White Papers: Background Materials, 1970 October (Box 106, Folder 1263)
  - White Papers: White Papers: Economic Growth, 1970 October 15 (Box 106, Folder 1264)
  - White Papers: Environment, 1970 October 11-30 (Box 106, Folder 1265)
  - White Papers: Federal-State Local Relations, 1970 October 13 (Box 106, Folder 1266)
  - White Papers: Health, 1970 October 16 (Box 106, Folder 1267)
  - White Papers: Higher Education, 1970 October 15 (Box 106, Folder 1268)
  - White Papers: Housing, 1970 October 17 (Box 106, Folder 1269)
  - White Papers: Law Enforcement, 1970 October 12-November 1 (Box 106, Folder 1270)
  - White Papers: Mental Health, 1970 October 30 (Box 106, Folder 1271)
  - White Papers: Mental Retardation, 1970 October 29 (Box 106, Folder 1272)
  - White Papers: Narcotics, 1970 October 28 (Box 106, Folder 1273)
  - White Papers: Parks and Recreation, 1970 October 31 (Box 106, Folder 1274)
  - White Papers: Power (Energy), 1970 October 24 (Box 106, Folder 1275)
  - White Papers: Primary and Secondary Education, 1970 October 12 (Box 106, Folder 1276)
  - White Papers: The Rights of Individuals, 1970 October 29 (Box 106, Folder 1277)
  - White Papers: The Rockefeller Team and Endorsements, 1970 October 15-29 (Box 106, Folder 1278)
  - White Papers: The Rockefeller Team and Endorsements, 1970 October 8-14 (Box 107, Folder 1279)
  - White Papers: The Rockefeller Team and Endorsements, 1970 May 19-June 25 (Box 107, Folder 1280)
  - White Papers: The Rockefeller Team and Endorsements, 1970 July 2-September 30 (Box 107, Folder 1281)
  - White Papers: Social Services, 1970 October 23 (Box 107, Folder 1282)
  - White Papers: Transportation, 1970 October 16 (Box 107, Folder 1283)
  - White Papers: Working People, 1970 October 31 (Box 107, Folder 1284)
  - White Papers: Youth, 1970 October 14 (Box 107, Folder 1285)